gospelhotspot.net 2018-12-20

# Gospel Hotspot Privacy Policy « GospelHotspot.Net

## Privacy & Cookie Policy

This Privacy Policy outlines how **Gospel Hotspot Media** collects, uses, maintains, and shares information gathered from users of [www.GospelHotspot.Net](http://gospelhotspot.net/). It applies to the site and all of the products and services offered by **Gospel Hotspot.**

### **Overview**

  1. Cookie Policy.
  2. What information we collect.
  3. How we use collected information.
  4. Where we store your personal data.
  5. How we protect your information.
  6. Sharing your personal information.
  7. How long we keep your personal information.
  8. Your rights.
  9. Third-Party websites.
  10. Changes to our privacy policy.
  11. Your acceptance of these terms.
  12. Contact.

### **Cookie Policy**

Our site may use cookies to provide a better experience for our users. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes, as well as for tracking information. You can set your browser to refuse cookies at any time, or alert you when they are being sent. Some aspects of the website may not function properly if cookies are refused.

#### **Our Cookies Are Used For The Following Purposes**

Category

| 

Description  
  
---|---  
  
Essential Cookies

| These Cookies are necessary to allow us to operate our Sites so you may access them as you have requested. These Cookies, for example, let us recognize that you have created an account and have logged into that account to access Site content. They also include Cookies that enable us to remember your previous actions within the same browsing session and secure our Sites.  
  
Analytics Cookies

| These Cookies are used by us or third-party service providers to analyze how the Sites are used and how they are performing. For example, these Cookies track what pages are most frequently visited, and from what locations our visitors come from. If you subscribe to a newsletter or otherwise register with the Sites, these Cookies may be correlated to you. These Cookies include, for example, Google Analytics cookies.  
  
Targeting or Advertising

| These Cookies collect information about your activities on these and other sites to provide you targeted advertising. We may also allow our third-party service providers to use Cookies on the Sites for the same purposes identified above, including collecting information about your online activities over time and across different websites. The third-party service providers that generate these Cookies, such as Google, Facebook, and Twitter, have their own privacy policies, and may use their Cookies to target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit to our Sites.  
  
#### **How Do I Refuse Or Withdraw My Consent To The Use Of Cookies?**

If you do not want Cookies to be stored on your device, click the button below to opt-out of all non-essential cookies and services.

If you want to remove previously-stored Cookies, you can manually delete the Cookies at any time. Please consult the help section of Your web browser to understand Your options, but please note that if You choose to disable the cookies, some features of our website or services may not operate as intended.

### **What Information We Collect**

**Information you give us.**  Information you give us may include your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and social security number. We only collect this information when you voluntarily give it to us. You can always refuse to offer any information, but it may prevent you from using some aspects of the site.

**Information we collect about you.**  This is information that we collect automatically about your visit during your time on the Site. It typically involves technical information including the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, IP Address, and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. This type of information is typically collected using small data files called cookies. This information helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the Site and also to indicate where the Site requires improvement.

**Information we receive from other sources.**  This includes information we receive about you from other websites we operate. The information in these cases will be gathered voluntarily with your consent.

### **How We Use Collected Information**

The information Gospel Hotspot collects from you, whether personal or technical, may be used by us for the following purposes:

  * To improve our customer service by responding to your requests more quickly and efficiently;
  * To personalize your experience on the site;  
We may use your information to better understand how our collective customers use our website;
  * To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services;
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature;
  * To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them;
  * To send periodic emails.

We may use your email address to send information and updates about your order. It may also be used to respond to questions or other requests. If you choose to opt in to our mailing list, you’ll receive emails that include Gospel news, updates, product information, and more. You can unsubscribe from our emails at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of every email sent.

### **Where We Store Your Personal Data**

All information that you provide to us is stored on our secure servers, and we will take reasonable steps to protect your information in accordance with this policy, including (but not limited to):

  * Encrypting data; and
  * Carrying out regular back-ups.

### **How We protect Your Information**

We use extensive security measures to ensure that your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data is safe from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or deletion. Any data exchange between you and our site happens over an SSL-secured channel, which is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### **Sharing Your Personal Information**

We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Payment Gateways.**  Gospel Hotspot does not process any payment information directly. We use payment gateways to process this data. These payment gateways have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

**Third-Party Provider Privacy Policies:**  

### **How Long We Keep Your Personal Information**

We retain your personal information for as long as you have your account. You have the right to request your information be deleted. (See “Your Rights” section below)

### **Your Rights**

You have the following rights under law in respect of your personal information:

  * The right to be informed about the collection and use of your personal information;
  * The right to request access to your information to be sure we’re using it legally;
  * The right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information about you is made accurate;
  * The right to request the deletion or removal of your information where there is no further reason for us to use it;
  * The right to restrict the use of your information;
  * The right to obtain and reuse the information that we have about you for your own purposes;
  * The right to refuse certain uses (such as for marketing purposes); and
  * The right to opt out of a decision that has a legal effect on you that has been based on an automated decision.

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may do so at any time by writing to us at the address below. (See the “Contact” section below)

If you would like to request the information we hold about you under a  **Subject Access Request (“SAR”).** (See the “Contact” section below)

If you feel that your rights have been breached in any way, you may reach out to as at the address below. (See the “Contact” section below)

### **Third-Party Websites**

You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

**Gospel Hotspot** has the choice to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### **Your Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the site after changes of policy will be regarded as acceptance to the changes.

### Contacting Us

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy should be addressed to **Ayodele Smart** at a **yodelesmart@gospelhotspot.net**

If you have any other questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

**Gospel Hotspot Media**  
www.GospelHotspot.net  
7 Difri Road, Anjorin  
Behind AIT, Alagbado Lagos  
+234-8034999090  
music@gospelhotspot.net
